So again, I click on "Pixler" to get back to the home page, and I click on "Open AI Photo Editor."
So as you see, plenty of tools available over here in this very home page.
Let me get back to where we were, yep.
We have "Pixler Express," which is the AI Photo Editor.
We have "Remove BG," which is "AI Background Eraser."
We have "Pixler Designer," which is template for template and animate.
We have "Pixler Editor," which is "Advanced Photo Editor."
And we have "Batch Editor," which is "Balk Photo Editor."
So I click on "I click on this Express," or "I click here."
Both will direct me to the very same page, and we're just getting started with it.
So it says "Modern AI Power Photo Editor" for quick and professional edits.
Let's do yep.
Thank you so much.
And I want to edit, right?
So as you see, we also have this image generator option over here.
So "Pixler" also provides us with the ability to generate images.
I click on this one.
I open it in a new tab, but for now, I just want to do an image editing
with the very tool.